Yassin El-Ghatrify: Hello, Machi.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Hello, Mr. Emad.
Emad Faheem: Hello, everyone.
Emad Faheem: How is everyone doing today?
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Well, alhamdulillah.
Machi: Hello, everyone. We'll get the meeting started in a little bit.
Machi: I got a bunch of messages. Some people will not be able to join today.
Machi: That sounds… We'll still go through what we need to go through.
Emad Faheem: Guys, I have a quick question. Does anyone have a problem with Discord? Since yesterday, my Discord is not loading.
Emad Faheem: And, like, I can see, like, people are sending messages, but I can't open nothing.
Emad Faheem: And I try, two different, PCs, try my phone, the same thing.
Emad Faheem: Anybody have the same problem?
Machi: Not with me. I'm not having any…
Ceren: provides.
Machi: Experiencing any issues.
John Hazlewood: I haven't had any issues either.
John Hazlewood: So, maybe it's your phone or something, maybe just reboot it, I don't know.
Emad Faheem: And.
John Hazlewood: Are you doing that on your phone or your computer?
Emad Faheem: Both. I I'm, like, I'm talking now from a laptop.
Emad Faheem: I work on a PC, and I have a phone.
Emad Faheem: And I have the account on all 3 devices.
Emad Faheem: And it's the same issue.
Emad Faheem: So I don't think it's a device.
Emad Faheem: It's something in the system, but…
Emad Faheem: I did check, like, ChatGPT, and it says in the US, USA only, not everywhere.
Emad Faheem: So, does anyone, from like, currently is USA, maybe experiencing the same thing.
Emad Faheem: I mean, if not, if you… if anyone, like, John, if you… if you know any, like, troubleshooting I could do, I appreciate the help.
Emad Faheem: I try to open and close, sign out, sign back in.
Emad Faheem: Restart.
Ceren: Yeah.
John Hazlewood: That was a question.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Hello, everyone. I'm so sorry I'm coming late. So what is going on, first of all?
mohamed abdelmohsen: I feel like you talk about something is, let's say, yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Hard, for example? What is the issue?
Emad Faheem: Yeah, for me, hi Mohammed, since yesterday, my Discord is not working.
Emad Faheem: And I have it on my phone, on my PC computer.
Emad Faheem: And it just… it says, like, cannot load, and then I'm not receiving any messages. And I did, like, search it, and they said it's, it's been… it's been happening since yesterday in the USA, not everywhere. So I was wondering if anyone, maybe in the USA have the same issue, or…
Emad Faheem: They just maybe… maybe it's just my account, I'm not sure.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I think I talked with Emily, Emily in USA, and I talked with her today, and it is working.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And, I think also, I'm not sure about Claudia. Did you check on Claudia?
Emad Faheem: I try to, like, text her in LinkedIn because I can't communicate with her on Discord. My Discord is not working.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, so, so, Ahmad, you can either take, the transcript from this meeting and take this part that we're talking about, or just ask ChatGBT and ask it if there's something going on in the last day, 24 hours, and if you can check
John Hazlewood: If it can… You know, check the internet.
John Hazlewood: So that way, it… it doesn't just use stuff from its memory or something, from the…
John Hazlewood: Model, because the model's not… I have to…
John Hazlewood: You know, there's a cutoff date as far as what it has in it, but…
John Hazlewood: And I'm sure Chat Gbt will tell you.
Emad Faheem: Yes, yeah, I got from ChatGPT, said it's since yesterday. Some places in USA.
John Hazlewood: Oh, you did? Okay.
Emad Faheem: Yeah. Yeah. I did. So if anyone is trying to communicate with me on Discord, it's not like I'm not responding. It just is not working. So, maybe we can connect on LinkedIn temporarily until, it goes back to normal.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, okay, this is something that we can consider, but as Jen said, if you can use a VPN, try to use a VPN, and try to use another browser when you log in to Discord, not the app, from your laptop. If you're using Google Chrome.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Use Safari, for example, or use whatever you have, like another browser.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You know, and try.
Ceren: maybe?
Emad Faheem: I'll check it out.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Ginger in.
Ceren: Firefox, maybe.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Firefox. Yeah. Yeah.
Emad Faheem: I will. I will. That's a good idea.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yep.
Emad Faheem: Thank you for your time.
mohamed abdelmohsen: at your service. So where is Machi? How are you doing?
Machi: I'm doing okay,
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay.
Machi: Wow. Not a lot of people showed up today. So.
Machi: We're just gonna go through what we can.
Machi: So I mean, we're already 12 minutes in, so I might as we might as well get started.
Machi: So, welcome everyone. I didn't prepare an agenda today, because today I was hoping…
Machi: We will just look through the
Machi: All the videos that were done over the past week.
Machi: And, I got a bunch of messages saying people will not be able to join.
Machi: And,
Machi: I'm looking at the Google Drive right now, and it would seem no one uploaded to the Google Drive.
Machi: She is very disappointing. I assume maybe some of you have your content on your laptop, so you'll be sharing screen. At some point during the meeting, but.
Machi: Let's… I guess let's go through…
Machi: So I'm gonna shh… The Google Drive in the overview.
Machi: It's the same one, no?
Machi: Do we have two?
Ceren: I mean, are you looking for the, waiting for approval?
Machi: No… The drive I have here… okay, let me just share my screen.
Machi: This one, so… So I put to this one.
Machi: And it's all these folders.
Ceren: Okay, go to…
Ceren: Okay, not… okay, I'm gonna send the link to you. There might be something you didn't see in here.
Ceren: Oh, delicious.
Machi: Do we have two Google drives?
Ceren: That's January 25th clips folder, but after that we opened a new one, FloLabs social media assets.
Machi: Alright.
Ceren: I sent the…
Machi: looking at.
Ceren: not.
Machi: Okay.
Ceren: I mean, I'm not sure if they're new other than what I uploaded.
Ceren: That wasn't showed before.
Machi: Okay.
Machi: This is… This is different.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Can you share your screen, Machi, please, again?
Machi: Okay,
Machi: This one.
mohamed abdelmohsen: loading.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Lucy's equivalent.
Machi: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You have my drive, and after that, at the header, you can choose yeah, this one.
mohamed abdelmohsen: If you open in on of Zeus like waiting approved.
Ceren: Waiting approval are the ones that all of us can upload.
Machi: Yeah.
Ceren: So for sure, will be later on, whoever in the marketing team says yes, or whoever the team lead manager, whatever.
Ceren: Can move to there.
Ceren: That was the system.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes. Can you open another one? Like the week before?
Machi: removal.
mohamed abdelmohsen: The other photo?
Machi: And this is strong.
Machi: Hold on, so if I were to… So this is… Flo Labs. Try. I see.
Machi: Okay, guess that I shared the wrong… The wrong one, and the…
Machi: The overview? Let me make that correction now.
Machi: So…
Machi: Okay.
Machi: Interpretive skills.
Machi: Credit of this one.
Machi: Okay, so, that's kind of what we're gonna do today.
Machi: Like, this, you know, he doesn't have anything in here.
Machi: And Ash, this was July 12th.
Machi: Okay, so I guess the first one I'm going to go through is Jira.
Machi: Okay, so you have one clip. Did you work with the people you are assigned with on this task?
Ceren: We met with Atenko and, talked about which parts of the video we can make content of.
Ceren: I decided that that was one part, and he made…
Machi: So it was just.
Ceren: so.
Machi: One video from the three of you?
Ceren: He made a carousel, but we didn't put that there. I can put it there as well.
Machi: Hold on.
Machi: I need to see who… I assigned this to…
Machi: Do you remember the one you were assigned to?
Ceren: you
Machi: Oh, no, sorry.
Machi: midweek.
Machi: Okay. And you were assigned with…
Machi: Nahali Nahali says she's in traffic.
Machi: And Nathaniel is not here. Okay.
Machi: Well…
Ceren: Yeah, he said something about.
Machi: Let's see…
Ceren: or.
Machi: terms.
Ceren: co-hosts.
Machi: That's a 9. Okay.
Machi: Who made the carousel?
Ceren: He did. Otanko.
Machi: We need to.
Machi: Let's take a look at the carousel.
Ceren: We will need to change that image, but.
Machi: Okay.
Ceren: No.
Machi: As soon as… Say we to.
Machi: Okay, just take a look at it as is.
Machi: Okay… Let's see…
Machi: How do your hardware arrives in 14 days, but your backend isn't ready? Do you write a code? What's this?
Ceren: He took the parts about… The Kaipo…
Ceren: Talk about the Kaipo and turn it into a carousel.
Machi: I wish she was here.
Ceren: foremost.
Machi: senses.
Ceren: Yeah.
Machi: of… Which is horrible, it's not working tonight.
Machi: He's right.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Thank you so much, Gene.
mohamed abdelmohsen: He's not here, and I think… Atanuku's not here, and I think he will not be here today, so if you want to lead this to the next meeting, maybe, when he shows up?
Machi: Yeah.
Ceren: No.
Machi: Okay, Let's take a look at what… Ceren, great.
Machi: Hold on, I might not be sharing audio, hold on.
Ceren: I just realized I still need to add subtitles or captions to that. But yeah, I'll do that after.
Audio shared by Machi: you.
Machi: Okay.
Audio shared by Machi: It's Julia from Italy, and when we talk about Italy, we talk about the skills and the beauty at the same time, so… Yeah. And we have Serene, and we have Indra eating ice cream.
Audio shared by Machi: Yes. Someone get bathed, guys.
Audio shared by Machi: Someone get paid!
Audio shared by Machi: Ha ha ha.
Audio shared by Machi: Okay.
Audio shared by Machi: Yep.
Audio shared by Machi: So, it's nice to see you all guys, and Indra, and we have Machi and Manny also. Yeah, it's good to have all of you guys here. So, are you able to lead the meeting, Indra?
Machi: Middle of an ice cream break.
Machi: Okay, what do we think? Could use some subtitles, yes.
Machi: Maybe, like, like a… like a bonk sound, or some sounds, like when you're switching. Between who's talking.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You know, guys, you can you can put some lights. You can you can put some lights, you know, at the back as I'm in the stage, and you can have two dancers beside me. Guys, what are you doing?
mohamed abdelmohsen: What are you doing?
Machi: This is gonna get clipped as well.
Machi: Fantastic.
Machi: It's probably gonna get clipped as well. Okay.
Ceren: We'll see if I.
Machi: Any thoughts?
Ceren: Just moment.
Ceren: Both the buses on your…
Machi: You can do it.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, yes, yes. You know, you have this tradition people that they have swords and dance beside you like this way, you know? So.
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's the most educational video clip that I've seen before, like, guys, you're talking about the AI, the robotics, all the stuff that we teach within the company, or everything that we make, yeah, so you're doing a good job, guys, you're doing a good job!
mohamed abdelmohsen: I have another word, but I can say it to Jerim, but I definitely can say it for Machi, but not in this meeting. I can say it to him after this meeting, not now. So…
Machi: I know what you're going to say.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Oh, okay.
Machi: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Jaren? Yeah. I think, Jaren, you can, yeah, take what Mohammed said in this meeting just a while in the last couple minutes.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Sorry.
John Hazlewood: about this.
John Hazlewood: Two girls, though.
mohamed abdelmohsen: John.
John Hazlewood: And then you can have that happen, you know. So he's talking about it, and then it happens. And then, you know, he's talking about learning, and and I think that would be a good way to finish this.
Ceren: Yeah.
Machi: I agree. So just for the sake of your notes, this was about 20-something minutes into the meeting, so look between 22 and 24, so just so you can time it properly.
Machi: I'm helping you out here. Thank you.
Machi: Okay, so a bit more editing, and then that can go.
Machi: So, for everyone else who's in this meeting, the Google Drive link has been shared. I'll probably just put it again.
Machi: In case you have…
Machi: In case you weren't able to upload your video to the Google Drive.
Machi: And that's the Google Drive link we're looking through right now.
Machi: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, hey Machi, just a little clarification on the time clip.
John Hazlewood: That you just showed Jiren?
John Hazlewood: Went to edit.
John Hazlewood: You showed her on Toggle?
Machi: On toggle?
John Hazlewood: Did you just show, like, the time to say you can edit here?
John Hazlewood: Where he was talking?
Ceren: The minutes between 22 and 24, I'm gonna check that and see.
Ceren: MOHAMED's speech, that's why he showed that time.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Basically, Mr. John, he is helping everyone right now. They give them directions, instruction, like, guys, don't bother yourself to even watch all the meeting, you know? You have those 2 minutes, you know? Focus, put all your focus on that, so… No, Mr. John!
John Hazlewood: No, but I wanted to, like, clarify, because…
John Hazlewood: That 22… between 22 and 24 minutes on your toggle is different than other people's that came in at a different time.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Absolutely.
John Hazlewood: That's not Zoom.
Machi: Right, right, right. Okay.
John Hazlewood: like.
Machi: switching.
John Hazlewood: Yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, she wants to do…
Yassin El-Ghatrify: I think in the future…
Machi: I see what you mean. It's because my timer… Yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You know, Mr. John, actually, what you did right now, I'm so sorry, I've seen. Actually, what you did right now, Mr. John, is right now, when they're using, like, what are Matchy talking about, maybe a difference between a person to another person. But right now, you give them, like, the 100% directions, so they're gonna use Toggle, check the time, so everyone gonna figure the minute, the second, everything, so…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Guys, I will delete this meeting after this meeting. I'm so sorry, guys. I will delete it.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: I think in the future, inshallah, when the company grows, Muhammad would be the perfect PR manager.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: The.
Ceren: I keep saying he's the face of the company.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Yeah, like we're gonna have.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: You should have a Muhammad body.
Machi: Isn't it beautiful?
Machi: It's beautiful. This one clip is generating more clips from this particular meeting.
Machi: It's beautiful.
Machi: Okay, thank you, Jaron.
Machi: We'll move on to Emad.
Machi: Nahu.
Machi: Oh, okay.
Machi: This should be fun.
Machi: What the did Nago do? Okay.
Machi: It was 8 minutes.
Machi: My apologies, I think my… yeah, my internet's not good.
Audio shared by Machi: I'm fine. I'm all right. Okay. Okay, I'm joining from Nigeria.
Machi: Hold on, is this the… the… The clip? The interview?
Emad Faheem: Yes, yes, it's the one we had, Maria and I, and it's not the whole thing.
Emad Faheem: Like, the whole conversation was over 30 minutes, but we kind of took parts just to show you something.
Emad Faheem: I think Maria also is working on something else.
Machi: Okay.
Emad Faheem: I couldn't coordinate with Maria because of my Discord problem, so I'm not sure if Maria, also got something. I just uploaded this right now when you shared the Google Drive.
Emad Faheem: So yeah, I'll say.
Machi: Maria is also working on something. She said…
Machi: Does she stock… I think she's also stocking traffic.
Machi: So it should be, like, 30 minutes or something late. She's in the meeting right now, but she's probably out, so she might not be currently available.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, I'm gonna go…
Machi: For me to watch this.
John Hazlewood: Are we gonna watch this? Because it's nine minutes.
John Hazlewood: Are we gonna… Watson, put some…
Machi: just I'll probably just skim through it and see what, you know.
John Hazlewood: Bye-bye.
Machi: highlight.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
Machi: Maybe.
Audio shared by Machi: My full name is Joe Chinagorom Bijoma, but people just call me Nago for short.
Audio shared by Machi: And I'm a certified pharmacist. I studied pharmacy.
Audio shared by Machi: In the University of Nigeria.
Audio shared by Machi: And
Audio shared by Machi: And my journey into the tech world started while I was in pharmacy school. I remember it was in my third year when I started.
Machi: No.
Machi: Skip to…
Audio shared by Machi: subsection of pharmaceutical sciences. So you get to learn a lot of things, aside everything that applies to pharmacology and other different.
Machi: Okay, so for us to really grasp
Machi: This, video, I probably will need, like, a… Question for context, and
Machi: And then his response for it,
Machi: Let's see if I can just pick, like, a random moment, maybe…
John Hazlewood: Yeah, and, and one of the things.
John Hazlewood: that we could do is, like, do 2X on the time.
John Hazlewood: Just in general, I've seen some
John Hazlewood: Some, influencer videos, they're speeding up the time so they can, like, keep it under, like, 60 seconds, let's say, or whatever.
John Hazlewood: The talk is a little bit faster, but you get everything, and it might be a good way, especially
John Hazlewood: You know, in certain parts that… I mean…
John Hazlewood: Maybe you can do it in some parts and not in others, but I think when you're editing that footage, Ahmad.
John Hazlewood: you kind of kind of think about that, because I don't know, I mean, I know this is for our reviews page, but for someone to sit, listen 9 minutes for a review, it might be a little much.
John Hazlewood: So… Yeah, I guess depending on where we're gonna post this, Oh.
John Hazlewood: you know, But anyway, think about that.
Machi: Yeah.
Machi: Emad, anything, do you have anything to respond with?
Emad Faheem: Yes.
Emad Faheem: What's the question?
John Hazlewood: No, it wasn't…
Machi: It wasn't really a question, I'm not…
Emad Faheem: No.
John Hazlewood: It was a suggestion, just to…
Emad Faheem: do.
John Hazlewood: When you're… when you're editing the content.
Emad Faheem: it's.
John Hazlewood: to do times 2 on the voice, and so it just… it could have been, like, half the time. Instead of a 9-minute video, it would have been a 4 and a half minute video, for example, or in parts of it, speed it up, and in other parts, again, I don't… I don't know who's gonna, like.
John Hazlewood: Even if this is on our reviews page, sit and listen to a 9-minute review.
John Hazlewood: you So…
John Hazlewood: Yeah, but anyway, that's… I've seen some influencer videos when I'm scrolling, and, you know, and they actually… I can tell that they speeded up the sound, so, you know, it goes a lot quicker, but those guys are usually trying to keep their
John Hazlewood: Their content under, like, 60 seconds or something.
John Hazlewood: And… Right, yeah, so that's what I was suggesting.
Machi: Oh.
Machi: Actually, it looks like Ash uploaded something.
Machi: 8 32.
Machi: Okay, so that's… so for, Emad and Maria, I think the video is good. Maybe we just take, like, clips, maybe 30 seconds to a minute.
Machi: of a moment…
Emad Faheem: I'm sorry, because I just want to clarify this part. Are you talking about reviewing during the meeting? Because the project is a whole another aspect. We spoke about.
Emad Faheem: Three things, and I think John was also, there.
Emad Faheem: One of the things was the episodes, like, to have episodes with each.
Emad Faheem: Each one of the, like, Flo Lab members.
Emad Faheem: And that will take, 20 minutes or more. So 8 minutes is kind of actually short for 20 minutes. That's one thing. Yeah. So are we talking about, like, in the meeting, to have, something shorter?
Machi: Yeah, yeah, for this particular meeting, the purpose of this particular meeting was, It's.
Machi: So for this kind of video will go well on YouTube. It's long form. Eight minutes is kind of long form, so it will go well on YouTube.
Machi: What I was asking for was, like, 30 seconds to a minute
Machi: 15 seconds, or maybe 2 minutes.
Machi: Something that can be short, sweet, will, have retention and rewatch.
Machi: And usually… and usually that's, like, short… really short form, 30 seconds, YouTube shorts, TikTok. type content, you know, so that's what I was asking for.
Machi: It's not this… this one is good.
Machi: Oh, there's more people uploading. This one is good. We'll probably have a separate
Machi: Maybe meeting to review this one.
Machi: But, yeah.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Yeah, I think it could be, like, the specific review…
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Like, the specific review on Flow Labs could be, like, a wrap-up question.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Like, 30 seconds at the end. So you could have both in one… video, essentially.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: And at the end, you could have, like.
Machi: solutions.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Saying, yeah, saying in, in 30 seconds, describe your experience.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Or, or how would you… Describe your experience at Flo Labs.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: And that's the final question in the… in that part.
Machi: Right now, I can tell I can tell Emad is Emad is a little disappointed.
Machi: And.
Machi: Because he's a little, he's a little, he's a little disappointed, Yeah, but I think it's.
Emad Faheem: Not because of the feedback.
Emad Faheem: Because I feel like, we spoke of many things.
Emad Faheem: And we… I did work on some of the things we spoke of.
Emad Faheem: And then we're talking about, like, you know, like, being selective about what we want, in particular.
Machi: Would.
Emad Faheem: Which is cool, I just… it's just not clear for me.
Machi: Oh gosh, come on now.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Machi's, yeah.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Disconnect.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Okay, but until Matchi comes back, what I'm just trying to say, Mr. Emad, is that you could have the podcast, you could have it in full.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: But… At the end, just so we could, like, how would you say it, like, probe.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: The ability to take it as short-form content, you could have, like, a…
Yassin El-Ghatrify: A quick question at the end, like a concluding question, or like a final question.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Where the participant summarizes everything at the end.
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's a good point that you address right now, Yassin, and I think also the other point that Emad and Maria is doing is actually we try to build a review base actually about every intern here within the company. So you can have a short clip for this person talk for one minute or two minutes, or even you can have.
mohamed abdelmohsen: the 7 or 8 minutes about his experience and all of this stuff, and we can have it on the website, like, honest, truth, real way, without any manipulation. So, we have both ways. You can create short clip, like.
mohamed abdelmohsen: For example, yes, hi, my name is Muhammad Abdulmohsen, I'm blah blah blah, and…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Please, Emad, don't share all the meeting, please. My meeting, especially. So, anyway…
mohamed abdelmohsen: let us try and seek the results, guys, because I know what we're talking about right now, I think, is the best solution. If you have kind of short clip with summarize at the end with a question or something.
mohamed abdelmohsen: it will be also a good thing we can work on that. So, I think we can work on what Emad is doing, and make some edit also for that, so…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Well… Yes, Emmett, please go ahead.
Emad Faheem: No, I'm just saying, I don't have any preference when it comes to which project to work on. I just want more clarification. Like, this is what we want you guys to work on. That's what I'm asking for. But for myself, I'm okay with whatever has been decided. That's all I want to say.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, this is more clarified. Please go ahead, Yasin. I know you want to say something.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: No, no, I wasn't.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Guys Yassin from the marketing team to he's the one who gonna call the shot. He and Emily for publishing everything. So yep.
mohamed abdelmohsen: When they say something, they mean it. So thank you, Yassin, for the updates, and I think Machi's not here. I'm not sure about… should I take it one by one for the updates, or should I continue what Machi's doing? So I think I will follow up with what Machi was doing. So let me share the screen.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And, continue, because I feel jealous, and I uploaded
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm not sure. Is it okay or not? But uploaded some.
mohamed abdelmohsen: of the meetings… What's this about?
mohamed abdelmohsen: No, we should skip this one.
mohamed abdelmohsen: What's this about?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Also should skip this one.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, skip this one.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, no.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Sorry, let me share the sound.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Can you all see my screen, guys?
Ceren: Yes, we can.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Gmail.
Audio shared by mohamed abdelmohsen: Flo Labs building the next generation of AI and robotics from intelligent assistance to space technology where humans and machines solve the impossible.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, it's not complete yet, but this is part of what I did.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Plus…
Audio shared by mohamed abdelmohsen: and performance data already exists, but it is trapped in different watches, apps, reports, and spreadsheets. Mood Changer brings those signals together. Powered by Flobrain.
Audio shared by mohamed abdelmohsen: The ecosystem connects authorized data, understands context, and translates complex information into clear, personalized actions.
Audio shared by mohamed abdelmohsen: HealthBuddy supports individuals with check-ins, records, reminders, trends and plain language insights. Athletic performance intelligence helps coaches and teams understand readiness, recovery, workload and performance. CAPO provides a wearable.
Audio shared by mohamed abdelmohsen: Multimodal way to capture context and connect with Flobrain. Future extensions can include biomarkers, e-research, and MoodChanger for pets. MoodChanger is not another dashboard, and it is not a replacement for qualified professionals. It is a software first.
Audio shared by mohamed abdelmohsen: Hardware agnostic ecosystem designed to help people understand what is changing.
Audio shared by mohamed abdelmohsen: Decide what to do next and stay motivated over time. Mood changer, from scattered signals to personalized action.
John Hazlewood: Mohammed, you showed us this last week, right?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Not in the GTM. I showed that at the marketing team, but none here show what they have.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: But anyway, guys.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, it's okay, Mr. John. Anyway, guys, I have the videos here. Just go there, check them, maybe. Let us see… So, we saw, Emad, let us see Maria.
John Hazlewood: I'm sorry, Mohammed, what was your point of that video? What were you trying to communicate with the team?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Actually, what I was planning to let the people see, like, the idea of if you guys gonna make videos, let's imagine you're gonna make AI videos. Try to make something educational.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Have, good enough information about what are you showing the people. And, like, when someone watches this clip.
mohamed abdelmohsen: from the beginning, you're gonna understand something. What I showed in this video, I'm talking about Mood Changer. What Mood Changer is, what apps that we're gonna have from this team, how it's gonna help the people, so…
mohamed abdelmohsen: This is the point.
John Hazlewood: Okay. But but I mean, I think we have a a our focus right now is only to create content using the the team meetings not to go out and produce.
John Hazlewood: Content like what you just showed us, right?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, yes, Mr. John.
John Hazlewood: Okay, I just wanted to clarify so no one gets confused here, because
John Hazlewood: I thought it's… it seemed like maybe, you know, it was indicating that people could go out and create that type of content. And I think we talked about also in the marketing meeting, that's a little bit… you did that some time ago, when the technology wasn't very good. It looks very AI-generated.
John Hazlewood: And…
John Hazlewood: Of course, we want to… we want content, we would publish that like… like it is. We would want to go through and make it look non… not AI-generated, because people's eyes glaze when… when it looks AI-generated, and it doesn't make us…
John Hazlewood: Put us in the same light, so we're trying to do that, of course, with everything, that, you know, our websites and, and, and, you know, everything that we're doing.
John Hazlewood: Our content, yeah, so…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, mister John. So guys, here is an example that even with the AI tools, it's not an easy thing to create a video right now. So it's not a simple thing to make. So we have the free meetings. We have everything, our meetings, our materials. So please use them.
mohamed abdelmohsen: try right now, at least don't focus on the AI tools to create video clips, because, as you see, I tried to use, the AI tools, actually, to create those videos.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And.
mohamed abdelmohsen: They are AI generated. The images, the cartoons, you can see, you can feel it. It's not that real. For some people, they're gonna like it. For other people, they will not. But the Flo right now is in the company, use the meetings.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: I have a question on that one. Has anybody here…
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Attempted to use the meeting clips.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: And use AI as, like.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: An assistant to edit those clips, turning them into more…
Yassin El-Ghatrify: appealing, like, like, something like how Diogo's video… Or Diego's video looked like…
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Like, how did Diego do his video?
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Did he use AI to take the clips we already had, and…
Yassin El-Ghatrify: use AI to enhance those clips, Into a… short form…
mohamed abdelmohsen: What video video? I'm not sure about what we're talking about. What video?
Ceren: As far.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: you.
Ceren: Diego isn't using AI. He just uses another app called Vegas Pro.
Ceren: Something like that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes.
Ceren: But I don't think he's using AI.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Yeah, so that's my question is, is I think we could upload The clip… On to AI.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: And then tell AI to enhance the clip.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: I actually edited it into a way that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: For, for short form content, TikTok and all that. Like we have them.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Absolutely.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: And we could put that clip onto… Yes.
mohamed abdelmohsen: absolutely.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: I don't know.
mohamed abdelmohsen: somebody.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: You tried it or not?
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Are there…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, Yassin.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: another.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, Ubisoft.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: So.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Obsclub, Obsclub. There's a website called Obsclub. You can upload the meeting, whatever, it's 1 hour, 2 hours, 3 hours, whatever. But if you just… if you just use it that, so what is the meaning of this meeting? What is the meaning of this team members, like?
mohamed abdelmohsen: What I did, actually, just I used the transcript within the meeting itself, and let him make me clips. They make, actually, 4 to 9 clips from, I… I recall it was 1 hour and a half, or 2 hours.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And all of these clips, I can use them. If you ask them about kind of educational, funny, anything, so completely.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Scratch or or it.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: It took the clip from the meeting and, and…
mohamed abdelmohsen: The clip itself. Yeah. Took the clip itself from the meeting itself. You know? The meeting. Yeah. So and even they make cuts. Like, if you talk about a point, let's say, at the first ten minutes.
mohamed abdelmohsen: about Mood Changer, and you talk about Mood Changer at the last of the meeting, the last 10 minutes, and you ask them about make me complete clips about, like, meaningful, something like that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: They're gonna gather the first, let's say, 2 minutes with the last 2 minutes, just in one clip, and when you hear it, you're gonna feel like.
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's not cut in between, you know? It's complete.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So without any eye manipulation, they just figure out the transcript, timestamped every section what they're talking about, and then they gather it.
mohamed abdelmohsen: It took… sometimes it took 3 hours to make it so, so you just upload it, and after you upload it, just keep it for 2 or 3 hours, and after that, you're gonna see the results. And you can use all of them, but in that case.
mohamed abdelmohsen: it will be, let's say, no need for this team, actually. Because, guys, you won't do nothing. And at the same time. With human attention, human manipulation that we are doing here, maybe you can make something.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Let's say more focused.
mohamed abdelmohsen: More than that.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: But we could… Like, I think we could choose the clips… themselves, The meetings themselves?
Yassin El-Ghatrify: But there, I could do all the… all of the…
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Manipulation of the clip to actually make it look aesthetically.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Pleasing, like, actually, because, like, to be honest.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: the standard for video editing on TikTok and Instagram and all these social media platforms, the bar is now so high relative to before, because people are using AI to edit their videos. So…
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Like… I think we should… Capitalize on the… that development.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: And now our role would be choosing the cream of the crop. You get what I'm trying to say?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, I get what you said.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: What do you think, Mr. John?
John Hazlewood: 2… Repeat what you said.
John Hazlewood: Well.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: What I'm saying is… That like Muhammad is now said the.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Sorry, I forgot the name of the program.
mohamed abdelmohsen: August Club.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Office Club.
mohamed abdelmohsen: or Best Clip.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Opus clip. He said that you could upload the recording.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: To their program, and it could edit it.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: And I.
John Hazlewood: I have transition.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Yeah, and actually refine the videos.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: aesthetic.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: And edit it.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Quite well, like, and, and can you prompt it?
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Muhammad or is it just Like, you upload the video and it works,
Yassin El-Ghatrify: By itself. Like, can you prompt it, and it gives you the video, and you say, edit this part, and it edits that part, and it…
Yassin El-Ghatrify: Like, it's back and forth?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, but simply the way I used, I just uploaded the video, asked him, like, I need to make reels, YouTube Shorts. That's it. No more than that. No more word. And click enter. Waited, 2 hours and a half, and I have 49 clips. Each clip.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Two minutes, one minute and a half.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You know.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: And… Edited, like, the editing quality itself, is it actually… High quality, like, the transition.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah.
Yassin El-Ghatrify: And like, I don't know if you were here last meeting.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You see?
John Hazlewood: Okay, we lost Yassin.
John Hazlewood: So I'm not sure what his question was to me. Why… is he asking me whether we should test it?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Mister John, what Yassin is talking about right now is using kind of tools like Obsclip and just upload the video there.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Small problem.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, I know. I understand. Is he asking me if we should test it?
mohamed abdelmohsen: I think yes.
John Hazlewood: Okay, well, yeah, yeah, test, please. Whatever, I mean, shouldn't have to ask to test things. Let's test whatever, you know, if there's some new tools out there, let's test them, see how they work. Absolutely.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay… where is the scene?
mohamed abdelmohsen: You have a task, Yassin.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, this is great. August Club. Machi, are you here?
Machi: Yeah, I joined again, but I might have to leave the camera off because it's it's still disconnecting.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Are you able to continue this meeting, or should I?
Machi: I… I think it's okay if you can continue, since you have your… Screen on, it's okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, my friend.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So I will just continue.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, Mohammed, I don't know how much time we have left. I think this meeting is supposed to be around an hour.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
John Hazlewood: But.
John Hazlewood: So…
mohamed abdelmohsen: I think we can follow another approach here at the last, let's say, 15 minutes, guys. I will ask everyone about what they did, the clips. Not sure for this, meeting right now, but we're gonna see that the marketing team gonna review each member work. So, I just want to share something.
mohamed abdelmohsen: First of all.
mohamed abdelmohsen: this place, waiting for approval. I can see Apapalui, Ash, Jerin, Ahmad, Maria, and me. So, for every person here, guys, you should log in. Create a new folder.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Name it with your name.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Noah. Whatever.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And after you create it, you're gonna have it, open it. When you have a video, click here, file upload, choose your file, upload your file, and that's it. No more than that. Waiting approval in this place. So I can see a Papalwi, Ash, Jerini, Ahmad, Maria, Mohammed.
mohamed abdelmohsen: We have more than, let's say, 30 person.
mohamed abdelmohsen: or more in this team. So, hopefully, the next meeting, I can see another folder for each person with their work, so the marketing team can see every person's work. So, this is the first thing that I want to talk about. The second thing.
mohamed abdelmohsen: We had for Reddit, actually, we had a task for Reddit. Every person should go there, take and give an honest, trustful comment, and make a post about the company.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I think…
mohamed abdelmohsen: This task was made two weeks ago. We didn't review the updates about this task, so I will take… I will give you all guys more time about that. Please follow this task that we did here.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Refresh. Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, now the number increased. Okay. Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, I will watch… I will not watch them, this meeting, because, guys, we're short on time, and I prefer the next meeting we're gonna have for each person, let's say 5 minutes, to see the updates, what they are talking, so we can have the updates from each person. This meeting should not take more than 1 hour, let's say 1 hour and 10 minutes.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, no more than that. So please, guys, you have two tasks. First, upload what you did in this place, whatever, yeah, okay, it is under 1 minute, 2 minutes, whatever the video that you have, as…
mohamed abdelmohsen: The only thing that we need with each video is just to have a meaning, like, and using our meetings to make this. So…
mohamed abdelmohsen: I will not talk anymore about the videos. The second task is Reddit. Please, guys, follow up with the Reddit task. Go there for the task that Jerry make. Please, for whom who don't have access to this task, don't recall the link, please send me a message. You know, I will share it in the general chat of the influencer.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And I think, now I'm gonna ask each person about what they did. So, hi Salwa, how are you doing?
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's not a tricky question. If you did something, it's okay. If not, please start from now on. I know you don't have enough time.
Salwa Akkad: Yeah, so I'm doing well. For what I've done as content, no nothing actually was done. I got yesterday added to a group with Yassin and someone else.
Salwa Akkad: That other person, like, clipped a video that is meant to be funny.
Salwa Akkad: but needed some editing to be as easy to find funny. So I suggested to Yassin a few moments ago that we should work on that, but I don't have access to Flow Labs CapCut account, so I said I wanted to reach out to you to get the…
Salwa Akkad: Account. So, yeah, I'll be reaching out to you soon.
Salwa Akkad: To work on this video and other videos. So yeah, that's on my side.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, let's say this is your kickstart point. Okay, don't bother, so… Buy guns is buy guns, as they say. So, we can start right now. I will forward every credential that you want.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Actually, right now, the Cockcat, everything. And, guys, for everyone else whom done with their master classes, please send me a message so I can give you all the AI tools access within the company. But we have a condition. Just done with your master classes.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Thank you, Sawa, for the updates. Hasna, how are you doing?
HASNAE: Good.
mohamed abdelmohsen: No, he did a good job.
HASNAE: I believe in that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You did a clip?
mohamed abdelmohsen: We didn't have enough, we don't have enough time to witness this during this meeting. Hopefully the next meeting we're going to do.
HASNAE: Yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: If you have time to make more, it would be great, yeah.
HASNAE: I just wanted to say that I wasn't, I didn't do it using AI, so I was inspired by the video itself.
HASNAE: To do highlights?
HASNAE: To do just highlights, and I did the editing. I did the editing myself, and at the end, I came to a video of one minute of highlights of the video.
HASNAE: The whole video.
mohamed abdelmohsen: As long the clip that you make have meaning.
mohamed abdelmohsen: We're gonna love it. Don't. So it will be accepted. Just meaning. Let the people understand something.
HASNAE: It's just highlights. Yeah, it's just highlights.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Well, we're gonna see it the next meeting, and hopefully gonna make more. Okay, thank you, Hatna, for the updates. Chilo, how are you doing?
Chilo: Hi, MOMED, hello everyone, I'm good, I'm fine.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, did you make anything related to the content creation team? Don't feel sorry if you didn't, you can start right now, it's not a big deal, but from this week, guys, no more… bygones is bygones, again.
Chilo: Yeah, I actually did something, like, the tasks I was assigned to, I actually did it, but, you know, it wasn't just me, it was I, I think Maria, and, Chidera.
Chilo: So, 3 of us were in the same group, and I don't know if…
Chilo: They are done with theirs, but…
Chilo: I'll reach out to them to find out, but I'm done with mine, so hopefully the next meeting we can present.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Great, guys. Great, thank you, Chilo, and prepare for the next meeting, because when we ask someone, he should present us some work, and I believe we're gonna like your work, Chilo. I didn't see your editing work before, but hopefully it will not be around me, so I'm gonna love it, hopefully.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Thank you, Chilo. Kevani, how are you doing, my friend?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Hmm.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Ivani?
mohamed abdelmohsen: We can hear you, my friend.
kevani minott: Oh, you can hear me?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Right now we can, right now we can. How are you doing?
kevani minott: I'm, I'm okay.
kevani minott: I'm still working on my master classes, I have 2 more to complete.
mohamed abdelmohsen: That's okay, that's okay, that's okay, my friend. So, this team actually work on creating some clips, some posts, some work that we can make to influence, the company and the teams and everyone here. So, hopefully the next week.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You're gonna done with your mask classes, and then we can have, like, the one-to-one meeting with Mr. John.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And then you're gonna have the AI access and all of the stuff. So please, man, make sure you're done with Zoom Masterclasses as soon as possible, because after that, you have your kickstart point within the company, okay?
kevani minott: Or…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Thank you, kevani, and how are you doing, Maria?
mohamed abdelmohsen: How are you doing?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: We can't hear you.
mohamed abdelmohsen: We can still hear you, and…
Maria Moner: Hello?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, now we can hear you, now we can hear you. I know you work with Ahmed on the reviews, the clips that you make with every intern here, and actually, it's a great job, the project that you work on with Ahmed, and I do believe you're gonna make a more wonderful job. So, my only question is you, for you is, did you make me something this week?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Hopefully not.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Buffalo.
Maria Moner: Yes.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Let's say yes, I hate you, Maria. I hate you, Maria. I hate you, Maria. Thank you! Guys, Maria is…
mohamed abdelmohsen: She's destroying me. My cousin's gonna kill me about what she's doing. So she understand. She understand. But yeah, thank you, Maria. If I killed one day, you're gonna be the reason for that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: No, kidding. Thank you, thank you, Maria, and thank you, Ahmad, for the updates. And we do have Mohammed Saeed. How are you doing, Mohammed?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Muhammad Saeed.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Saeed.
mohamed abdelmohsen: The other Muhammad.
MOHAMED SAEED: No, great, how are you?
mohamed abdelmohsen: How are you doing, my friend? I told you before.
MOHAMED SAEED: the.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Only Muhammad here. Change your name, man, and your password and your.
MOHAMED SAEED: I.
mohamed abdelmohsen: and everything. I'm the only Muhammad here, man.
MOHAMED SAEED: You are the older Muhammad.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm just kidding.
MOHAMED SAEED: This is Fajera.
MOHAMED SAEED: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, yes, my friend. So, are you done with your master classes?
MOHAMED SAEED: Yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Great, so you're now part of the team, so I assume that we can make the one-to-one meeting?
mohamed abdelmohsen: With Mr. John, and after that… no, before that, I can assign you, give you right now, actually, the AI tool access, so you can use them. ChatGPT, Claude, Cursor, everything, CapCat, the group account, so you can use everything from now on. And hopefully, soon, we can make the one-to-one meeting.
mohamed abdelmohsen: But the next week, please.
mohamed abdelmohsen: should at least make one video, two videos, whatever the amount that you can make, using the meetings that we have, like, the weekly meetings that we have from the interns. Try to find something useful.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Because we're gonna publish that on the social platforms, YouTube, Instagram, TikTok, everything. So, this is actually, let's say, the main task for this team is to make
mohamed abdelmohsen: Content for other people.
mohamed abdelmohsen: To use within the social media platform.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Please let me know that you understand the main task of this team, actually, right now.
MOHAMED SAEED: I didn't understand, especially…
MOHAMED SAEED: What from the, the meetings? What do we…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, so we'd have, more than 18 meetings a week, you know? We published that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: About the IoT, the front end, the back end, the Sunday, the mood changer, every team, we have meeting for them. So, the idea is to use any of those meetings, and I prefer, if you are part of those meetings.
mohamed abdelmohsen: those teams, because you're gonna understand what this meeting is talking about, so you can just, let's say, me talk about something useful, about an idea, AI,
mohamed abdelmohsen: something on the edge that the people can understand and help them, and promote the company also. So you can use this time, 1 minute, 2 minutes, whatever, just use Kakat.
mohamed abdelmohsen: that we're using for editing the video, cut the videos, the clips, make a video from 1 minute or 2 minutes or more, it depends, and then, as I showed you on the Google Drive folder, just make you their new folder and upload your file there.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Did you get me now?
MOHAMED SAEED: Okay.
MOHAMED SAEED: Yeah, yeah, I get that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And guys, if any one of you guys have any issues, don't understand anything, just want to understand what is going on, please reach out to me, reach out to Jiren, reach out to Maria here. So reach out to Nago. We're gonna help you.
mohamed abdelmohsen: we can help you. Just send a message about something you don't understand, or you don't feel like something is not correct there, so we can help you. Okay, thank you, Muhammad Saeed. Is it Saeed or Saeed? Because some…
MOHAMED SAEED: Right.
MOHAMED SAEED: SAFE.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Said? Said?
MOHAMED SAEED: Hi, Yo. Yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, Egyptian, Egyptian Muhammad Said.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Salwa is smiling right now. Yes, I'm in Egypt, sometimes I can't understand English, yes, I'm ignorance, yeah, I'm ignorant at this age, yeah?
Salwa Akkad: I got the privilege of understanding whatever you say, guys.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, if we speak in Arabic, she gonna she will not understand. No, someone from Lebanon, yeah, yeah. But I I feel HASNA, if we talk in Arabic, she will not understand anything.
HASNAE: I do understand. I do understand. I do understand. You don't understand Moroccan, but I do understand Egyptian.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You know, guys, I just want to say this. We have more than, let's say.
mohamed abdelmohsen: 18 Arabic countries around the world.
mohamed abdelmohsen: If we have people from the right country or the left country, whenever, sometimes they don't understand each other. So, actually, try to speak in Egyptian, in our language, in Egypt language, so each other can understand each other. So, if you come, someone from Saudi Arabia, talking with someone from Morocco, to understand each other, they should choose.
mohamed abdelmohsen: A Middle Arabic language.
mohamed abdelmohsen: We choose Egypt.
HASNAE: If they.
mohamed abdelmohsen: If they speak in Egypt, they're gonna understand each other, but if they still talking in the same language, they will not. So sometimes speaking English is more better than speaking Arabic. So…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, anyway.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Thank you, Hasna. Thank you, Muhammad Saeed. Thank you, Salwa. Do we have something? Yeah, please! How are you doing, Xinyi?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Chini.
Xinyi 'Feliz' Ge: And
Xinyi 'Feliz' Ge: Hi, can you hear me?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes. We can hear you right now. How are you doing?
Xinyi 'Feliz' Ge: Okay, yeah, yeah, my connection is not good right now, but.
Xinyi 'Feliz' Ge: It's okay. Like, last week, we just… we are just trying to catch up with the post, and the Mood Changer post, Dina, right now, Dina, has picked it up first, and, there's… there's another post, John suggested the athletic
Xinyi 'Feliz' Ge: performance intelligence post on LinkedIn, the content creation, and that's what this team is working on for us. And, I'm doing okay. Last week, we'd just be back from a biomechanics conference, so I was completely traveling the entire time.
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's okay, please. You can do whatever you want. Guys for whom don't understand, Xinyinim means ovens.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So something.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Like, they have a good… they have a good name. You have a wonderful name, Chini. Chini means abundance.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Oh my gosh.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I love your name, Chini, by the way.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Don't take it.
Xinyi 'Feliz' Ge: And.
mohamed abdelmohsen: In the wrong way, I love your name, so don't take it in the wrong way, please.
Xinyi 'Feliz' Ge: Okay, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, thank you. I like my name, too. This is my name.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, great, great. So hopefully, you can contact more with Dina to figure out the post and make it as soon as possible. And if you have more time, also, you can spend… you can work on… create some of the clips that we work on right now. And I do understand you, understand what is going on, so the next week, we're gonna ask every person, actually.
mohamed abdelmohsen: each person about what they did, check their folder, see the updates, and what they did. So, please, Chini, the next meeting, be prepared to show us that, and I'm pretty sure… I'm pretty sure you're doing a good job. So, thank you, Chini, for the updates.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And, guys, did I miss anyone? I think Emad talked, AC talked, so I think… No one is missing, so please, guys, the next week.
mohamed abdelmohsen: we're gonna do the same as I mentioned right now. Everyone, every folder directory on Google Drive, we're gonna review that, see what we did, whether it was a club, a post, whatever you're working on. And if any one of you have any blockers, anyone don't have AI access.
mohamed abdelmohsen: like, for the AI tools that we have right now, please, please send me a message right now so I can grant you the credential and grant you the access.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, Mister John.
John Hazlewood: I'm sorry, I just wanted to ask, I know, Emad and Maria, the… those… those clips.
John Hazlewood: And, I mean, I think those… Whatever we have, even unedited.
John Hazlewood: are… are okay for, like, our… we're on the Flow Labs page, we're gonna put Flow Labs slash reviews.
John Hazlewood: And… Have kind of the clips with the… with the team members there and the… and the content.
John Hazlewood: And MOHAMED, I think we had our deadlines probably passed right now because we wanted to have something up, you know, something initial.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Sergio.
John Hazlewood: For a dollar.
John Hazlewood: Do we have something?
mohamed abdelmohsen: The program… the program is settled. Yes, we're done with it. I just need someone from the marketing team just to make the summary, and just the transcript and the link to add it.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So I can think… I do think that, the next meeting, I can share it with the marketing, and after that, just one hour, and you're gonna see the result on the website. I will make it myself, so don't worry about that.
mohamed abdelmohsen: But I need someone, actually, just to make it. I can do that!
mohamed abdelmohsen: like, the summary, the meeting, post the link, so I can even work on that. But the idea is, you told me, like, you need to have
mohamed abdelmohsen: Five or six or ten meetings, not only one meeting in the beach.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Am I correct?
John Hazlewood: I mean, right now, started off with as many as we have, but Maria had mentioned that there was 14
John Hazlewood: I think something like that that had already been
John Hazlewood: Meetings that you've had with people?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Talking about the reviews?
mohamed abdelmohsen: The reviews, or the weekly meeting.
John Hazlewood: No, not the weekly meeting, the reviews.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I didn't work on that, but it will not take too much. Half an hour, and I can have it on Stravi also. They they can pass the link for these meetings. And if we have it or they can add it actually as a video there.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, yeah, we can add it even as a clip there.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, it will not take too much from my side. I can work on that. Actually, I can work on that after we're done today. It will not be a big deal. I like to create a Starbi project for them, so they can post the clip, and they can make a summary, and the transcription for that, if they want it.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So.
John Hazlewood: the.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Action.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, that's what we have to do, is the summary.
John Hazlewood: I mean, the summary is really for the entire videos. For these clips, I mean, even if they're 8 minutes, ideally, even we'd like them shorter, but…
John Hazlewood: But if they're 8 minutes… with…
John Hazlewood: Yeah, we need to kind of look and see, do we have a summary for those, or do we just go straight to the transcription?
John Hazlewood: You know what?
John Hazlewood: So… Yep.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I can add the file. Like, I can make it to have
mohamed abdelmohsen: The clip itself, as a clip, as a video.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Or, also, I can have it as a link.
mohamed abdelmohsen: And I will make two places for the summary and the transcript as not required field. That means they can add it or not. But anyway, at the end, I just need… at the beginning, I just need to use the clip itself, so after that, I can have the transcript and all of that. So, I can do that, I can do this.
John Hazlewood: Okay, and it would probably be good, I don't know if…
John Hazlewood: either, you know, Emad or Maria, or maybe Yassin, he's in the marketing team, but,
John Hazlewood: Yeah, the tags that we have on those pages, and I don't know, like, when, Google…
John Hazlewood: you know, or the LLMs.
John Hazlewood: They they pick things up and they go through the websites when someone asks a question. So just to kind of identify the structure of the page.
John Hazlewood: So our plan is to have, say, 20 video clips, maybe with a summary, you know, or a paragraph or something, then the full transcript.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Ask the… ask ChatGPT, like.
John Hazlewood: How should the pages be structured? Should we have any specific terminology or keywords in there that will help SEO and LLMO?
John Hazlewood: Usually, like, there's, on the websites, you've got title tags, H1 tags.
John Hazlewood: Where you put certain… certain information that the search engines pick up.
John Hazlewood: But yeah, so we're working with, with.
John Hazlewood: The other team members, as far as the website.
John Hazlewood: In general, but since you're working on this one specific page, you know, to see how… do we do something different with this, with the reviews page?
John Hazlewood: From.
John Hazlewood: Because, yeah, and once we have the reviews here, then, I mean, we're also going to want to look at the different websites that we have to put reviews on every one of our websites.
John Hazlewood: So, even for…
mohamed abdelmohsen: So, John.
John Hazlewood: Even for like Kypo, for example, you know, someone talking about Kypo in one of our meetings and we can edit that out and just use that.
John Hazlewood: You know, even kind of… I mean, temporarily.
John Hazlewood: So I don't… I don't know how we wanna… Yeah, do…
John Hazlewood: Reviews for Athletics, Performance, and Intelligence.
John Hazlewood: And for Robo Collective,
John Hazlewood: You know, we don't really have reviews, but it'll be a little bit more complicated, but I think
John Hazlewood: Again, having something, some type of content.
John Hazlewood: But anyway, we can think about that. I just wanted to bring that up as far as the research for Flow Labs reviews page.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, Mr. John, let us start with Flow Labs Innovations. Today, I will make it sure that I configure that with Stravi, so the marketing team can just go there and feed the information, and even I will make a test.
mohamed abdelmohsen: with, let's say, a local website for… a local version for Labs Innovations, and I can show you that, let's say.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Tomorrow, maybe, I can show that as a demo for you. And then after we agree on that, we can push it to the website, and after that, even the designers can use it and make it more good appealing, the page itself.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So… I think I should have someone as a body with me within this task, guys.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So… I do know Maria and Emad. They are the guys who did attend with me the Stravi project.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So guys, do you have any time?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Today?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Actually.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Anyway.
Emad Faheem: Yeah, today's gonna be tough for me, Mohammed, I can't do today, I'm sorry.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Anyway, guys, I will work on that today, if anyone have time. Two hours from now, I will start to work on that. Anyone have time, please join, just to see what I'm doing. You're gonna like that at the end. You will not like it at the beginning, but you're gonna like it at the end. Because after this, if you are a front-end engineer, that means
mohamed abdelmohsen: You can be a full stack developer.
mohamed abdelmohsen: In a small way, not in the big picture, but…
mohamed abdelmohsen: You can have full stack website.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Anyway.
John Hazlewood: Strut.
mohamed abdelmohsen: interrupt.
John Hazlewood: Strapi's a content management system.
John Hazlewood: Where all this stuff is going to be hosted, so when the people come to the website, it pulls out of the content management system instead of pulling from a web page, which makes it a lot slower and much more difficult to maintain and update.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Absolutely, Mr.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay, I think it was a good meeting. We didn't talk too much. We didn't present a lot of work today, but hopefully, the next meeting, we're gonna present more. And I'm so sorry that Machi had.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, not a good internet connection. Hopefully the next meeting he will have. So guys, please, if anyone have any blockers, as I said, reach out to me, Jiren, Maria, Nago, we're gonna love to help every one of you.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So that's it for this week, and see you soon. Bye, bye.
John Hazlewood: Bye, thank you, everybody.
mohamed abdelmohsen: One second.